[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 13]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
“Unsoiled Starlight” ]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
Shu Tinglan.
Can we grab dinner
and talk?
No, we can't.
Shu Tinglan.
You refuse to communicate with me.
Where exactly do you place me?
The position of a client.
It's after work hours now.
You're back.
Time to eat.
Shushu.
I know you're in a bad mood today.
So I specially ordered a big meal
to keep you company.
How's that?
Thoughtful, right?
Yes.
You're the most thoughtful.
So—
You just apologized to Wen Jian like that?
Mm.
What else could I do?
Face isn't as important as work.
Besides,
I think Lawyer Xiao is right.
Avoidance is useful,
but you can't run forever.
Only by facing the problem
and solving it
can you grow.
Then what about Zhuo Yu'an?
If I were you,
I'd steal him right from under Wen Jian.
He's not an object.
What do you mean, steal?
Besides,
Zhuo Yu'an and I
haven't even established a relationship.
Whoever he chooses
is his own business.
Well, well, Shu Tinglan.
You’re totally desensitized
to Wen Jian now.
And emotionally—
you can pick it up and let it go.
A role model for us.
Not bad.
I'll reward you with a big rib.
Eat up.
Mm.
[Special Inspection Report on
Intellectual Property Risks]
Mr. Zhuo.
The current progress and issues
are these.
Anything involving
designers with personal trademarks—
copyright fees need to be paid separately.
This wasn't reflected in the report.
I'd like Lawyer Shu to give me
an explanation.
Copyright disputes are a big issue.
Zhuoyuan doesn't want to stumble
on something like this.
Indeed.
The version Lawyer Zhang just presented
had certain problems.
It was our oversight.
It's a very basic mistake.
I can't help but question
whether Lawyer Shu's report
is professional
or accurate.
[Special Inspection Report on
Intellectual Property Risks]
[Menu]
What everyone is seeing now
is the latest version in my hands.
It's been repeatedly checked.
All patent and copyright ownership
is very clear.
There are no problems whatsoever.
I take responsibility for
the report I issued.
And I can say with certainty
that in contracts with Zhuoyuan Tech
as the subject,
there are no copyright disputes.
Your guarantee is useless.
I hope the lawyers cooperating
with Zhuoyuan Tech
can always maintain professionalism.
What do you think?
Mr. Zhuo.
It's not that serious.
Just be more careful next time.
[Scope and Methods of Verification]
Anyway,
this cooperation with Hongzheng Law Firm
has been quite pleasant.
Now there's only the final
delivery stage left.
I'll rely on your continuous support.
These past days, colleagues
and partners—
thank you for your hard work.
To express our gratitude,
Zhuoyuan Tech
has provided internal benefits
for everyone:
free whole-home installation of
Zhuoyuan Tech's new products
and deployment of smart systems.
Please give your residential addresses
to the tech department.
By the way, Tinglan.
How could there be a mistake
in the company asset equity documents?
Jiajia didn't give my
final version to Zhuoyuan.
I'm not sure
if she did it on purpose
or just forgot.
Jiajia was careless about this.
You need to be more careful from now on.
Okay.
Mr. Zhuo.
Morning, Mr. Zhuo.
So early?
Outside business.
Yes.
Tinglan and I are going to Shengpurui
for the final handover verification.
So early to discuss business?
What a coincidence.
I'm going to Shengpurui too.
I'll drive you both.
Thank you, Mr. Zhuo.
Lawyer Shu.
These are our company's core documents.
Normally,
they're absolutely not allowed
to leave the premises.
But since Zhuoyuan Tech requested it,
we'll trustfully
hand them over to you.
Understood.
Thank you very much.
We'll certainly keep them safe.
We'll return them as soon
as we've verified them.
Good.
Then you two go ahead and check.
Mm.
We'll be going now.
-See you.
-Let’s go.
The car's here. Let's go.
You sit in the front.
What are you looking for?
An important articles of association
document is missing.
I'm guessing it's probably
near Shengpurui.
I'm going back to look for it.
Mr. Zhuo.
This is my problem alone.
It has nothing to do with
Hongzheng Law Firm.
If you're going to blame someone,
blame me.
Did you hear what I said?
Zhuo Yu'an.
Are you even listening to me?
This really is my problem alone.
It has nothing to do with them.
Zhuo Yu'an.
What are you doing?
In your eyes,
is the company
a place where I make arbitrary decisions
without reason or sense?
Stop looking.
[Articles of Incorporation of Shengpurui]
Found it.
Great.
How did you know it was here?
I can't give it to you yet.
I need it.
Mr. Zhuo.
This really is my problem alone.
It has nothing to do with
Hongzheng Law Firm.
I really do need it.
I understand Mr. Zhuo's intention.
You plan to hold a public accountability.
But Mr. Zhuo is someone
who values work procedures, isn't he?
This matter
is currently still an internal matter
for our law firm.
Could you
let us handle it ourselves?
Thank you.
[Zhuoyuan Technology]
[Articles of Incorporation of Shengpurui]
You'd better give me
a reasonable explanation
before this blows up.